<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<team>
<!--
  technikum29: team members (english)
	This XML file is read by PHP/SimpleXML.
  ATTENTION! This file has to be wellformed XML. All opening tags
	have to close again or use the syntax <img/>. HTML entitites are not supported,
	use special characters (UTF-8) instead.
-->

	<member identifier="sven" full_name="Sven Köppel" is_active_blog_author="Yes">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-sven.jpg" />
		<img class="photo" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-sven.jpg" />
		<abstract>
			<a href="http://svenk.org">Sven Köppel</a> is one of the three children of
			the founder of the museum, <a href="/heribert-mueller/">Heribert Müller</a>.
			He is a researcher in theoretical and computational physics.
			Sven is contributing to the <a href="/">technikum29
			computer museum</a> since more then 15 years.
		</abstract>
		<biography>
			Sven Köppel (born 1989) is one of the three children of the museum founder
			<a href="/heribert-mueller/">Heribert Müller</a>. He is contributing to the
			museum since more then 15 years. The focus of his work was the interfacing
			of legacy paper based storage media (paper tapes and punch cards) to the
			contemporary computer world. This was the foundation of exchanging
			program codes over the internet and to effectively allow collaborators to
			write (contribute) codes from remote. Furthermore, Sven was active in
			all kind of organizational topics, such as the museum outreach and
			paedagocical topics. Personally, he was living for half a decade in Frankfurt
			am Main, where he obtained a physics degree in 2019. In his research, he
			got an expert in high enery physics and computational physics. Since
			some time, he is living with his daughter and wife in the north of
			Germany (city of Münster/Westfalia; close to Hamburg).
		</biography>
	</member>
	
	<member identifier="roland" full_name="Roland Langfeld">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/photo-rl.jpg" />
		<img class="photo" src="/shared/photos/blog/photo-rl.jpg" />
		<biography>
			Dr. Roland Langfeld (born 1957) is physicist and holds several leading
			positions at
			<a href="https://www.us.schott.com/english/">Schott AG</a>, such
			as the head of R&amp;D, research fellow and consultant. Since early
			childhood, he is interested in all kind of technology. In 1977 he
			built up his first micro processor system. He collects old computers,
			pocket calculators and chess computers. He is a passionate programmer
			for all architectures.
			Since 2016, he is working with Heribert Müller in the technikum29
			for programming various computers and interfaces. Roland Langfeld
			is married, has two children and lives in Frankfurt.
		</biography>
	</member>
	
	<member identifier="juergen" full_name="Jürgen Müller">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/juergen-mueller.jpg" />
		<img class="photo" src="/shared/photos/blog/juergen-mueller.jpg" />
		<biography>
			Dr. Jürgen Müller (born 1963) is also physicist. He is leading the
			development of optical analysers for biological and pharmaceutical
			research at <a href="https://www.perkinelmer.com/">PerkinElmer</a>.
			He spends his spare time with any kind of vintage mechanics,
			electronics and computer technology.
			<br/>One of his archivements in the museum is the FPGA rebuild of the
			exact curcuit of the serial computer architectures of the 40s and
			50s with its drum and runtime storages. At the moment he encountered
			one of the few original tube computers in the technikum29, it was
			immediately obvious that he will be helping to restore this
			computer.
		</biography>
	</member>
	
	<member identifier="bernd" full_name="Bernd Ulmann">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/bernd-ulmann.thumb.jpg" />
		<img class="photo" src="/shared/photos/blog/bernd-ulmann.jpg" />
		<biography>
			Bernd Ulmann (born 1970) was a collector friend of the museum's founder
			Heribert Müller. He also delivered several talks at the museum during the
			"Woche der Industriekultur" in recent years. His main interest are analog and
			hybrid computers but he is also fond of early DEC machines such as PDP8/12/12
			and early VAX systems. Other areas of interest are classic oscilloscopes etc.

			He lives in Hettenhain with his wife, cats and analog computers and develops
			modern analog and hybrid computers. He has a professorship for business
			informatics at the FOM in Frankfurt/Main.
		</biography>
	</member>
	

	<member is_dummy="Yes" identifier="you" is_active_blog_author="Yes">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-you.svg" />
		<abstract>
			<em>Probably you?</em>
			If you want to write something, you are very welcome to send
			us texts <a href="/en/contact.php">by mail</a> or to contribute directly
			<a href="https://github.com/technikum29/technikum29-www">via Github</a>
			(it <a href="https://github.blog/2012-12-05-creating-files-on-github/">is easy</a>).
		</abstract>
	</member>
 </team>
