<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<team>
<!--
  technikum29: team members (english)
	This XML file is read by PHP/SimpleXML.
  ATTENTION! This file has to be wellformed XML. All opening tags
	have to close again or use the syntax <img/>. HTML entitites are not supported,
	use special characters (UTF-8) instead.
-->

	<member identifier="sven" full_name="Sven Köppel" is_active_blog_author="Yes">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-sven.jpg" />
		<img class="photo" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-sven.jpg" />
		<abstract>
			<a href="http://svenk.org">Sven Köppel</a> is one of the three children of
			the founder of the museum, <a href="/heribert-mueller/">Heribert Müller</a>.
			He is a researcher in theoretical and computational physics.
			Sven is contributing to the <a href="/">technikum29
			computer museum</a> since more then 15 years.
		</abstract>
		<biography>
			Sven Köppel (born 1989) is one of the three children of the museum founder
			<a href="/heribert-mueller/">Heribert Müller</a>. He is contributing to the
			museum since more then 15 years. The focus of his work was the interfacing
			of legacy paper based storage media (paper tapes and punch cards) to the
			contemporary computer world. This was the foundation of exchanging
			program codes over the internet and to effectively allow collaborators to
			write (contribute) codes from remote. Furthermore, Sven was active in
			all kind of organizational topics, such as the museum outreach and
			paedagocical topics. Personally, he was living for half a decade in Frankfurt
			am Main, where he obtained a physics degree in 2019. In his research, he
			got an expert in high enery physics and computational physics. Since
			some time, he is living with his daughter and wife in the north of
			Germany (city of Münster/Westfalia; close to Hamburg).
		</biography>
	</member>
	

	<member is_dummy="Yes" identifier="you" is_active_blog_author="Yes">
		<img class="thumbnail" src="/shared/photos/blog/blog-author-you.svg" />
		<abstract>
			<em>Probably you?</em>
			If you want to write something, you are very welcome to send
			us texts <a href="/en/contact.php">by mail</a> or to contribute directly
			<a href="https://github.com/technikum29/technikum29-www">via Github</a>
			(it <a href="https://github.blog/2012-12-05-creating-files-on-github/">is easy</a>).
		</abstract>
	</member>
 </team>
